Um I want to sort of chat a little bit
today about code assisting and actually
how we can how we use that in production
for for for real code that runs kind of
real business processes and um not just
kind of throwaway demos. So how how do
we use those tools in production?
Um I guess before we sort of kick off a
quick bit about myself. So I'm I'm Matt
Belchure. I sort of head up emerging
tech for in the in the UK. So a lot of
work over the past sort of year or so um
around AI quite a lot helping
organizations of understand and sort of
cut through the hype um but also trying
to adopt AI tools and AI services kind
of in the in in their workflows.
Um little quick bit about coants as
well. So we're a consultancy with the
values of software craftsmanship um and
XP kind of at our heart. Um and we're
all about really sort of trying to kind
of raise the bar of software quality
kind of in the industry. Um then as as
Sam quite nicely said, we also have um
we were born out of the London software
craftsmanship community um back in 2010.
Uh still very strong um sort of 15 years
later. Um I think it's about 6,000
members now in total. So really good
community um full of like-minded folks
that really care about building software
and kind of building it building it in
the right way.
Right. So I guess let's sort of jump
into it then. So this term kind of vibe
coding has been kind of used quite a lot
over the past few months. Um
who sort of have a guess or kind of
shout out what they think vibe coding
actually means before we sort of dig
into it. So what what does vibe coding
mean to anyone? Shout out raise your
hand.
Anyone want to have a go?
Slot code. Slot code. Okay. Yeah. Anyone
else?
Yeah. Prompting prompting. Yeah. Okay.
Not caring about quality. Not care about
quality. Yeah. Okay. So, some good some
good yolo. YOLO. Yeah. Okay. So, in
fact, it kind of came from this tweet
back in back in February. So, one of the
co-founders of OpenAI
um back in February. So, not long ago,
but it's become quite a mainstream term
already. Um it's quite quite a long
tweet but the first sentence said
there's a new kind of coding called I
call vibe coding um where you fully give
into the vibes
embrace exponentials and forget that the
coding even exists so on and so forth.
So there's there's quite quite a long
long tweet there but in effect what he's
basically saying is kind of I'm giving
over everything giving over control and
power to the the AI tooling and the LMS
and letting letting them run with it
really. sort of seeing seeing what comes
back. Um I think that can be quite
useful, right? Like that definitely has
some use cases and and that's let's have
a quick chat about that in a second. Um
but also I think there's some times when
that approach
is so
sides but um in terms of I think kind of
like vibe coding and like where it
really excels
in my experience so far like these are
sort of the patterns where like vibe
coding kind of works works really well.
So rapid prototype. So for example
within cojerance and so we've seen some
really good successes with building
quite rapid prototype tools with with a
vibe coding approach. So in fact some of
our colleagues who are even nontechnical
or or less technical they've been able
to build very quick applications to to
demo an idea or showcase or or a new
feature. So that's a kind of a class
that is very good at um sort of
discovery
um sort of technical spark
investigations
the sort of scaffolding code if you like
around applications and kind of boiler
plate code um they're sort of the
situations where I think kind of that
vibe coding approach can can work well
but I think if you look at all of those
sort of scenarios and situations they
tend to all kind of share a few sort of
common traits I going that are
interesting.
Um,
so the code generally has quite a short
lifespan in all those situations. You're
going more about speed. So I want I want
to build something very quickly to to
kind of prove an idea or work out what I
should do next or where should I invest
my time next or is this worth investing
further or so forth so on and so forth.
Um and generally like the the
functionality that you're building. So
you want to see this this feature um
that tends to kind of outweigh the code
quality. Right? So I think someone
mentioned before about code code swap um
with a vibe coding approach actually
that's probably okay because you don't
really care about the code quality. You
care about is this feature demoable? Is
it going to work in practice? Is my idea
feasible? those those kind of things.
Um, but I think crucially in all of
those cases on the previous slide, the
code's not going to run in production,
right? So, it's not code that's going to
support some really key critical
business process. Um, it's not customerf
facing or those kinds of things. So, I
think that's a really critical piece to
to kind of have a think about.
So if you kind of go back then to
talking about vibe coding and perhaps
why it's not so great for production. I
g back to the same tweet. It's kind of
there a few parts of that that I thought
were kind of worth highlighting a little
bit.
Um so I'm just going to read through a
few here. So forget the code even
exists. Um accept all always. I don't
even read the diffs anymore. the code
grows beyond my usual comprehension.
Um, great for kind of throw wind weekend
projects. And finally, like it mostly
works. Like none of those things to me
kind of sound like that's how you should
be treating production code, right?
And kind of hope that that's not that's
also not how you're treating your
production code.
Um, but I think then
a lot of people that I speak to kind of
equate AI coding tooling and AI code
assistance with kind of vibe coding. I
think there's they're two separate
things, right? I think we can still use
AI coding tooling and AI code assistance
tools for production code. Um, but we
have to do it in the do it in the right
right way. Um, web coding doesn't mean
that we have to follow follow that
approach if we're using AI coding
tooling.
But thinking about most of our jobs as
developers and we're building code
that's running in production, we kind of
want a bunch of qualities from that
code, right? We want we want to be well
understood for example. So I've been
reading about the code that's coming
back and understand it. We want to be
welld designigned for some reason. So we
want to understand is this design
aligned to my business goals and my
overall architecture. Is it evolving in
the right way?
uh is the code scalable? So if I go into
new markets, is the code going to still
hold up? If I add more users and more
more traffic, is is the the code going
to still be performant?
Um maintainable. So production code
lasts for many years as opposed to weeks
or months. And so being able to maintain
the code over time is very very
important because here you're you're
requiring changing that code over and
over again. So that's a key a key
feature. Of course testable as well. So
we want to be able to test the code and
make sure that it's surrounded by safety
nets that we can change it safely. Um of
course secure is obviously really
important. we saw a lot recently, you
know, in the in the retail space, what
can happen, you know, if if the code's
not secure
and of course performance and and a
bunch of other quality metrics there. So
quality does like code quality is really
key and really important for
writing and maintaining production code.
And so this this kind of idea of vibe
coding doesn't really fit with any of
these things, right? they don't really
kind of match the the criteria that we
need for production code.
Um
so how can we use these tools these kind
of these AI code assistance tools how
can we use them for production code? Um
if if it's not vibe coding then what
what's the approach? How how do we use
these tools?
And so at Cojant, we've been using these
tools now on like real world production
systems, real world code. We've been
leveraging tools like cursor and GitHub
copilot and uh clawed code, those kind
of things. But but we've been doing it
in a way that kind of following certain
principles and certain patterns that
govern how we how we interact with these
tools. And so I'll talk a little bit
about kind of what that what that looks
like.
But kind of at a at a high level, how do
how do we try to embed embed these tools
into how we work with production code?
And I think there sort of two two main
bits to it, right? It's like kind of
combining
the benefit and the power of these kind
of AI coding tools, but also not losing
sight of the the good kind of
fundamentals of good software
engineering that we all know and love.
um and kind of doing it in a way that's
a disciplined approach to how we kind of
interact with the LLMs and the coding
tools.
And so there's so we kind of have a
bunch of principles in terms of how how
our teams adopt uh AI tooling on on
client projects. Um I'm going to talk
through is that five? Yeah, five
principles today. Um there's many more,
but I'll just talk talk through talk
through five today. um in terms of like
what's guiding us for using these tools
in like production real world systems
that are supporting customer traffic and
customer businesses.
So the first one is kind of uh
maintaining ownership and control of the
design. So the name of these tools are
AI code assistants, right? So it's
important that they remain as assistants
and they don't take control of the code.
So we really think it's important to
have that kind of human in the loop
approach
uh for how we how we use these tools. I
think particularly if you're using um
agentic modes and cursor or co-pilot um
it's all too easy to to get to lose
control quite quickly because that the
amount of code that these agent
authentic features can can churn out is
is massive, right? And if you're not, it
all looks quite plausible. Um, but the
the amount of load that puts on you to
to understand like code all in one go is
quite quite a lot. And so we tend to
prefer having quite a strong human in
the loop approach where we're analyzing
and reviewing the output that's coming
back from these tools and just kind of
making sure that yeah, that's still kind
of going in the right direction through
our codebase and their architecture or
actually that's good but it's not quite
there. Let's kind of refine that little
bit. So making sure we get that get that
in there and making sure that we as
developers are still sort of driving the
bus in terms of the overall design and
the development of the of the code.
The other one I think is a big one which
is um prompt engineering. I think that's
become a is already quite an important
skill. I think this will be a critical
skill I think for software development
going forward. I think the way in which
we as developers kind of interact with
LLMs is going to be I think a critical
skill that I think all of us need to
kind of um re really hone and develop
over time. So
it's things like uh know one shot
prompting few shot prompting where we're
giving the we're giving examples in the
in the prompts that we're passing to the
the LLMs
but also like refining the way in which
we interact and being quite precise
about what we want to come back from the
the LLM
I think' be really really important. Um,
so I like things like breaking down
tasks into into smaller tasks. I think
like so it's very easy to to give quite
vague and high level prompt to your LLM.
I think if you do that, yes, you'll get
you'll get a response back and yes, that
will be a plausible response back. Um,
but actually is that is that right for
your codebase? Because what you're doing
there is you're opening up you're
opening a lot a large window for the LLM
to make assumptions about what's what's
right for you in your codebase and
chances are like you won't be making the
right tradeoffs for your particular
situation. So the more guidance you can
give in your in your prompts and the the
more examples whether it's using one
shot or few short approaches I think it
all kind of helps in terms of you
staying in control but also like
refining the quality of the output that
the LM can provide.
I also think
where we are seeing it inurance is
seeing the prompts becoming like
artifacts in themselves within the
software development process. I think
increasingly I think like the prompts
that we use to interact with the tools I
think they're going to be first class
citizens in themselves. So I think kind
of ving versioning those will be
important kind of sharing those across
your team. Having them sit either
alongside the codebase or in a separate
repo of themselves I think will be a be
a common pattern I think we'll start
that team will start to do. Um, so I
kind of recommend that as an as an
approach that is worth following. Kind
of versioning the prompts,
sharing them across your teams and kind
of refining them as you go. Um, but also
storing them alongside your your code.
I think a big one as well for like for
for us is trying to measure the impact
that we're seeing from the the code at
all adoption.
So like one thing is yes, we're going to
adopt these tools, but actually kind of
are they helping us in the in the right
way. So lines of code produced isn't
really kind of a meaningful metric
really. Um even if you ask a developer,
do you feel more productive and he or
she says yes, that isn't really enough.
I think you want to be looking at like
applying a sort of an approach here
around sort of systems thinking and
think about the whole SDLC as a whole.
Are these tools actually giving you the
benefit and the value that you really
need? So are are you able to ship
changes quicker to your your customers
for example? Um so are you seeing a
decrease in lead time? Um are you seeing
a decrease in change failure rate
because the code quality is improved for
example? If you think about SDLC as kind
of a a system, quite often
the the software development part of
that isn't the bottleneck, right? And so
being able to produce code faster by
leveraging AI tooling
that might actually highlight pressure
points elsewhere in your software
development life cycle that you might
need to kind of address either with or
without AI tooling. So I think it's
really crucial to think about how you're
measuring the impact of these tools. Um
so whether that be like the door metrics
for example or some other metric but the
metrics should be I think aligned to
your business goals and like the wider
SDLC system as a as a whole not just
kind of individual productivity or l
lines of code.
Um, next one here is kind of all about
experimentation. So, I think like we've
all we've all seen kind of how how fast
the uh the AI tooling space is moving,
right? There's kind of a new tool every
half an hour it seems. Um, which is
exciting, but I think also it means that
as as developers and engineers, we have
to kind of be be across that. So,
there's new tools, there's new models as
well. I think kind of know only recently
um claude 4 came out earlier in the year
I think February it was 3.7 so the gap
between them is sure thing it seems um
techniques as well so we're seeing new
techniques emerge around kind of AI
development and kind of refining those
so I think all of this means that if
we're if if we're not careful about kind
of how we start to adapt some of these
things it could get a bit like the wild
west I think with lots of different
tools and techniques kind of flying
around. So, I think it's important to
have a bit of a framework for how you
experiment with new tools, whether that
be AI code assistance tools or or new
kind of AI services or or APIs.
Um, and then kind of how you progress
those from kind of experimentation to
something that you want to kind of push
forward to and have that as a first
class tool in your organization or where
you actually you think no that's not
really kind of adding value for me. I
don't want to progress with that. So
some of the things along the lines of
the tech radar I think
what's the maturity of this particular
tool I'm I'm experimenting with is it
adding value yes or no is it worth
widing the adoption in the organization
or not. Um I think having that sort of
provides you as a kind of mechanism then
for how how you validate new tools. I
think I think it's important for
developers and development teams to to
have to have a way of experimenting with
these tools. Um but also you want to
experiment in kind of a control
controlled manner. So I think
particularly in the in the AI tooling
space things things are moving so quick.
Um it's important that there's that
space and and freedom to to experiment.
um particularly with I think the models
that they're improving so quickly that I
think it's important to be across that
but I think it's also important to sort
of have some governance around that that
says okay yeah we're confident that this
actually is kind of worth pushing now
into general use
um and then I think finally the final
one here is um that we see a lot of um
customers still sort of triing
uh like cursor or co-pilot but using the
free tiers or like personal individual
licenses. Um I would say try to try to
avoid doing that. I think it's it's far
better to to go with organizationalwide
licenses. Um and you might actually say
well we're not we don't want to tie
ourselves in too much with these
licenses because the tooling is moving
so fast. I I would say okay well maybe
sort of try kind of a monthly or
quarterly license but still have an
organizationalwide license because a lot
a lot of benefits to doing that versus
having it over kind of individual uh
free tier three free tier license. Um so
some of them include for example the the
privacy mode that you can enforce. So
yes as an individual you can toggle that
on and off. Um so your data is not being
used for not being saved away and
potentially used for training later on.
Um an organization level you can enforce
that that's not happening and be be
comfortable and confident that no data
is going to go to the outside world and
is going to be potentially used for for
training further models. Um it also
means that you can track usage and
adoption across your organization and
and across your teams. there's
dashboards that are available for the
for these tools here that show you what
people are doing um in terms of like
their model usage, their interaction
with the tool. Um these are all useful
data points I think for you to think
about is the adoption working, is it
adding value, are people using it, so on
and so forth. Um then of course there's
the the cost management piece as well.
So centralized bidding is also uh an
important thing here. Um I think also
lastly kind of the integration with your
existing system. So security is
obviously a really important piece. Um
these uh organizationalwide setups um
gives you the chance to sort of key into
your single sign on um mechanisms and
those kind of things. So you get that
extra layer of security around around
some of these things. So definitely
worth um adopting that approach if you
aren't already.
Um
just fine. So a little bit of kind of
how we're what we're seeing right now
within code. So I could share a few more
but just to sort of give you three in
terms of kind of some of the some of the
wins that we've been seeing with using
tools like GitLab copilot and and cursor
but in in production by using some of
these principles that I talked about
today. So it's still leveraging AI
coding tooling but doing it with all
these guard rails and principles in
place. So for example, we've been able
to see some of our time some of our
teams have reduced refactoring time by
50%.
Um so autogenerating the code but doing
it by specific refined prompts that
enable us to do that do that faster. Um
we had one one project where they were
migrating their their front end
framework to another one. Um the work
was kind of estimated as being being
several weeks worth of work. Um we
leveraged uh I think cursor did the
digital work um and the team did it
safely and
securely in a number of days. So it just
shows you the power of these tools and
also using them in kind of a controlled
and principled way. Um
then the very end one there is
we had a client where they had a very
large complex code base um that hadn't
been written test driven from the
outset. So there was lots of code that
wasn't covered by tests.
Um and add adding tests for for code
that wasn't tested is often quite a
difficult thing to do quite a complex
thing to do and quite time consuming.
um but they wanted to change his code um
but had a safety net of of tests around
it. So so the team leveraged kind of AI
tooling to add a suite of tests around
some of this code before being able to
make changes to it and we did that with
AI tooling and increase the test the
test coverage sorry by 30%. So again,
the first kind of three examples I could
show a lot more, but just kind of shows
you that
by using AI coding tools in production,
combining them with good governance and
principles, you can see, I think, some
quite good wins here. Um, so it's not
all about vibe code here. I think you
can still get some good successes by
using them in the in the in the right
way.
Um, so I guess back up then a little
bit. Um, so I think vibe coding, you
know, it has sort of dominated a lot of
the the airspace. I think over the past
couple of months or so. Um, I think
there lots of different interpretations
people have of kind of vibe coding and I
think people often kind of equate vibe
coding as being using AI tooling. They
are very different as the tweet
hopefully kind of pointed out. Um, and
vibe coding does have some some valid
use cases I think. um prototyping,
discovery work, technical spikes, those
kind of things. Um but for me at least
kind of vibe coding, that's not
something that you should use in
production.
Um I think for thinking about how you
then adopt these tools on enterprise
production grade code, it's thinking
about making sure that you have a clear
set of principles that that guide your
adoption. So your your team should know
what are the use cases that I would want
to use these tools for like what what
types of features should I be using when
might I use for example a genetic
features versus no genetic features
um what are some of the principles that
we want to follow around like prompt
engineering and how they're going to be
sharing the prompts those those sorts of
things and I think also like it's it's
going back to some of the fundamentals I
think and not losing sight of the fact
that we learn to get good at writing
software through some of these kind of
fundamental software engineering
principles. Um I think AI doesn't kind
of invalidate those. If anything else
kind of makes them even more important I
think so good design is really key
testable code all these good things. Um
but I think we still want to leverage
the AI tooling but we want to do it in a
way that doesn't compromise the good
software design fundamentals.
Um, and then
I shared I think four or five things
that we're doing within Cojer. So
maintaining control over the the code
that's generated, making sure that
you're the one driving the bus as a
developer and it's not the AI kind of
taking over. Um, I do think it is worth
kind of heavily investing in prompt
engineering as a as a as a skill, as a
practice within within your teams.
Getting good at that I think will be
really really powerful. Um and having
those prompts become kind of first class
citizens within your your teams I think
will will be a very valuable and kind of
beneficial thing to to do. Um think
about the overall impact. So not the
kind of adopting them for adoption sake
but actually kind of are you adopting
them and seeing the value that you
expect to get for to get from these
tools. Is it kind of improving the
overall software development life cycle
as a whole? Are are you seeing lead
times for changes? decrease. Are you
seeing code quality get better? That
those those kinds of things um and then
finally kind of I think it's really
important also along with the AI tooling
to have that experimentation culture. So
giving your teams the space to to try on
new new tools or new AI models as they
come out,
get a good sense of what's what's worth
kind of promoting from experiment to
general use um which things aren't. but
doing that in a safe and controlled way
and having kind of guard rails around um
how experiments then kind of progress
into general general use.
Um
just one more thing. So we are about to
kind of publish a kind of fuller report
on on this. I think that should land
next week. Um
keep an eye on that that website there.
that there's a kind of fuller report
that we that we we're going to publish
around AI code adoption for for
production. So I shared a snippet today,
but there's lots more that we kind of go
into in terms of those those practices
and the recommendations for your for
your teams um on how to use these tools
for production. There's lots of material
out there in terms of like using AI
tooling for PC's and demo wear, but I
think like there's not that much
material on kind of how to use these
tools for for production. So hopefully
that provides you with some some useful
guidance.
Uh I think that's all I have. So yeah,
thank you for listening.
We have time for questions. Few
questions. Any questions?
I was gonna ask how do you deal with
human fatigue
time?
Yeah, I think could you just repeat the
question? Sorry. Yes, the question was
how how do we deal with human in the
loop fatigue where I think the the
change set is is so large it's kind of
accept accept accept the change coming
through from the AI tooling. Um yeah,
good question. I think the key thing
that we tend to try and do is break
tasks down into smaller tasks and work
with the the LLMs on those smaller
tasks. So in fact, we often sort of
follow a bit of a bit of a loop on this
one. So we might start with a high level
plan for a piece of work. We'll work
with the LLM on on defining that plan.
So we have prompts that can help us to
sort of break down that into a set of
set of tasks. And so we'll be kind of
doing a few back and forth with the LM
to to create that that plan
as a human. And then we're reviewing
that plan and then we might get say five
to 10 uh incremental steps if like
within that plan and then what we'll do
is we'll then kind of go to an act act
phase where we're working our way
incrementally through those smaller
steps. So I think rather than having
quite large changes coming from the AI
tool league, you're getting much smaller
changes. So you're still I think driving
the bus in terms of like the overall
plan and you're helping and the AI is
helping you with that plan but you're
working in smaller smaller segments. So
it's leveraging AI tooling all the way
through but doing it I think in a
slightly more controlled controlled way
I think you were first. Yes.
what AI tools are you currently using
and do you have any like tricks that you
managed to figure out
more ways of using so what tools are we
using and do we have any tricks that
we've been adopting to make them easier
to work with um so I think there's two
main ones that we've been using which is
GitHub copilot uh and cursor um we also
have a little bit of um Jet Brains Juny
that we're using as well and uh some
experiments going on with claude code.
I think in terms of tips and tricks um a
lot of it is on the prompting side. So I
think kind of investing in refining the
prompts that come back um we tend to
disable the agentic features
um for most of our work, not all of it,
but most of it. And so that enables us
to I guess like control the amount of
change that comes back at any one time
and have a bit more of a
uh smaller smaller change set that we're
working specific specific get
um specific specific prompt. Yeah,
specific
I think I I can't give you a specific
prompt, but I think we've definitely
seen benefits in I think I mentioned it
earlier. um uh one and few shot one shot
and few shot prompting. So if you're
working on say a bit of validation logic
say rather than just kind of having that
as a high level prompt we might say okay
well here here's one example input and
here's what here's what the output
should be and here's another input and
here's what the output should be. So
it's it's almost like kind of like test
cases in unit testing but we're giving
it to the the AI prompt. And so that
enables the AI prompt then to be a bit
more smarter about response that comes
back. I think if you're using
um like cursor I think leveraging cursor
rules is also very good because that can
that can sort of do a lot of the heavy
lifting in terms of making sure that the
response that comes back from the tool
is aligning to your coding practices and
your coding styles. Um, but I think a
lot of it, yeah, a lot of it tends to
come with the the prompting techniques,
I think, as opposed to like specifics,
if that makes sense.
Yeah. Still on the prompt engineering
slide, the question is uh what kind of
uh prompts would you recommend to
versioning rather than not?
Uh so the question was what kind of
prompts do we recommend for versioning?
Um, how you mentioned that the slide
like Oh, sorry. Yeah. Okay. So, good
question. I think um
how I how I sort of see kind of prompts
evolving is I think they'll they'll be
as valuable if not more valuable than
the code that gets produced some in some
ways. And so I think the the code that
you're eventually like like the plan
before I think so I think taking a user
story and kind of how we how we plan
that not for the specific story but the
structure I think that sort of like
prompt templates almost you love that
phrase the prompt template I think be
something that I would be looking to
version control because that's something
that's quite reusable whereas like not
so much the specifics of an individual
prompt for a particular situation. I
think the the templates are things that
you want to focus on versioning the
most. Now, there might be situation
where
a specific prompt for a specific
situation is really useful and you're
seeing that come up over and over again.
I'm thinking things like um so we do
quite a lot of work where we're
analyzing code bases and looking for
like high level indications of like
domain boundaries for example that's one
where you would perhaps you want to kind
of have that as a prompt that you could
version and so if you want to get a
quick indication of is is the co is this
code base healthy
are the domain boundaries sensible I
think you could create craft a prompt
there that is will be reusable across
teams.
Thank you.
Amazing.
One more. One more. Sorry, I can see you
there. Thanks.
Um
do you tend to like generate supporting
documentation or files whatever to like
help the context when because I imagine
like every day you start working on
project or a colleague anybody else pick
a task and do you have like any other
generated documentation or how do you
help the context because you know
switching by models. Some contexts are
huge, some contexts are small like you
know depends on the model. Uh so do you
sort of reindex the project in some ways
to help the LLM understand what the
other work or not? I see. So um do we do
we index the project like uh for
instance for my job what we do like is
to generate to ask the LM to generate a
context file that describes the project
LLM. Oh I see okay got itself but I
don't know if it is the best way to do
it or not like or you start from scratch
every day like I see what you mean. I
think when we first start working with a
brand new codebase with a customer for
the first time, I think we would do a
bunch of um investigatory
I guess like context for us like
prompting to get sort of a lay of the
land. So yeah, we we want to understand
um like what how is the codebase
structured like where where are the main
functionalities? What are the main user
journeys through the application? what
what's the diabetes that are being used
the tech sacks and we we'll we'll store
that away somewhere um and that's sort
of the the high level context if you
like so if we have new people joining
the team they can take that prompt and
and they can run it and they'll get the
sort of the on boarding almost for free
coming from the LLM and the good thing
about that is that as the code base
changes that the prompt is obviously
going to reflect that so
um but of course I mean if you're
um cursive and code product that's doing
some indexing for you as well with the
embedding. So you you'll get some of
that for free. Um we've been playing
with uh claude claude code quite a bit
internally um for like larger larger
codebase exploration and having some
quite good wins with that um as opposed
to the generation part of cloud code but
leveraging that more for
explor exploring larger code bases and
asking it questions around
um like what functionality exists or
like um the libraries that are in use or
like the domain structures, those kind
of things.
Cool.
Cool. Thank you. Thanks,